export const Newfaqs = [
    {
        question: "Why buy YouTube views from Views4you?",
        answer: "Since the start of our company, we have always ensured that every one of your needs is met with unrivaled quality. As a manual team who manually checks all products for authenticity before they are delivered to you – there’s no better option than us! We are the only company that offers a complete package of products for publishers, including high-quality views for YouTube ads and high retention views. Views4You care about our customer satisfaction, so our customer support team provides solutions on the payment process a few hours after you make the purchase. We also care about your pocket; our services come at rock-bottom prices so that you can afford them! We offer a refill package money-back guarantee on all of our products, so there’s nothing you can lose when you give us a try. Other packages we have include premium-quality views for 1000 views or less!"
      },
      {
        question:"Do Views4You's YouTube views affect YouTube ranking?",
        answer:"We know that many factors affect YouTube ranking. When these elements come together, YouTube automatically sends you more viewers. The title of your video, your video description, and the thumbnail pictures you use for your videos are some factors that directly affect your ranking. In addition to these factors, buying high-quality views can also be among the factors that affect your ranking positively."
      },
      {
        question:"Does it take a long time, and how do YouTube views increase?",
        answer:"First, you go to our YouTube views service and send your video link to our system. Right after you buy views for your YouTube video, you can see the incoming views on the video statistics page within an average of 10 minutes! For slow viewings, the daily rate is around 2000 views on average, but for immediate viewings, this can be up to 10,000+ views per day. The reflection of the views just below your YouTube video may take up to three hours, depending on YouTube."
      },
      {
        question:"Is it legal to buy YouTube Views?",
        answer:"Yes, of course, buying YouTube views is legal in all countries. However, buying views are not in line with YouTube’s terms. YouTube works every day to make this and similar services impossible. Views4You, on the other hand, is trying to do the service it provides in line with YouTube’s terms to fulfill the demands of its customers. As long as you buy real video plays from real YouTube accounts, the number of views of your YouTube videos will continue to grow organically."
      },
      {
        question:"Why do people need to buy real YouTube views?",
        answer:"Standing out from the crowd on YouTube is not easy, and it’s even more challenging to appear on the search results when you have a small following or no one. That’s why purchasing YouTube views increases your Social Media engagement; as a result, your YouTube video views impact your ranking on YouTube’s search engine."
      },
      {
        question:"Can I choose the YouTube views location?",
        answer:"Yes! Of course, you can. We currently send you views from the USA, England, Spain, Italy, Japan, Korea, Brazil, Indonesia, India, and Israel. We are adding new countries to this list depending on the demands of the target audience you want. After clicking the buy button, you will be directed to the page where you’ll enter your video link. After that, our system will automatically determine your video’s language and suggest that country to you. We offer many services at affordable prices to help you get more views for every video content you share. Similarly, you can buy YouTube subscribers, or YouTube likes and also, you can buy YouTube lives stream views in the same method but on different pages."
      },
      {
        question:"Are YouTube views real when people come from Views4you to watch my YouTube videos?",
        answer:"Yes! We guarantee that the views come from real people and regularly optimize our systems accordingly. You can confirm that the views you buy from us are real. How? Once the views start coming to your video, look at your statistics page and observe where the views are coming from. We have an efficient screening process through which we filter out any spam accounts that have yet to show the right amount of credibility and legitimacy on YouTube. Again, you can observe the authenticity of views yourself since you will also start to receive active subscribers automatically to your channel, not just views."
      },
      {
        question:"How to grow my brand with YouTube views?",
        answer:"Views4You will not only get you more views, but you’ll also be able to create other strategies that will lead to more exposure and brand awareness. Using our specific customized techniques on our YouTube growth services, you’ll learn how to ensure that your target audience watches your video content. We’re here to help you gain more exposure on the YouTube platform to grow your social media presence and become a leading influencer! Ready? Just read on, choose your package, and let’s get started!"
      },
      {
        question:"1 million YouTube views is how much in costs, if yes is it possible to buy it?",
        answer:"Views4you is the best place to get as many views as you like without any limits. We will help you increase your views to up to 1 million YouTube video views and more, if you like, with our service!"
      },
      {
        question:"Can YouTube views decrease after I make the purchase?",
        answer:"Purchased YouTube views will stay on your channel, but if it ever happens that YouTube views go down, we’ll make it up for free for 60 days!"
      },
      {
        question:"How long will my videos be watched?",
        answer:"We cannot guarantee exactly, but it should be a minimum of 1 minute of watch time on average."
      },
      {
        question:"There is a country restriction on my video. Does this affect your work? ",
        answer:"If your channel has a country restriction, unfortunately, we cannot offer you our YouTube views service. We recommend using other promotional strategies to get more views for your YouTube channel."
      },
      {
        question:"How many views should I buy?",
        answer:"Your YouTube promotion decision is totally up to you and what you want for your YouTube channel. But remember that the more views you buy, the higher your chances of getting the popularity you want on YouTube."
      },
      {
        question:"What is the difference between your fast views and slow views service?",
        answer:"The difference between buying the Fast or Slow YouTube views service depends only on how quickly you want your video to get views."
      },
      {
        question:"Are YouTube views fake an option to buy?",
        answer:"Yes. Of course, you can buy fake views for your YouTube videos. But if you can buy real YouTube views from Views4You, why would you need a fake one?"
      },
      {
        question:"Does buying YouTube views have an impact on visibility in search engines like Google?",
        answer:"If you paid attention while searching on Google, you must have noticed that YouTube includes the most watched videos on the first pages. If the YouTube views you purchased have a high-quality source (Views4You gets its traffic from within YouTube), it will positively affect both YouTube SEO and search engines. Don’t forget that the YouTube views you receive from Views4You come from only real accounts bringing more YouTube views real and quickly to your network."
      },
      {
        question:"Will others know that I bought views?",
        answer:"The great thing about purchasing YouTube views from Views4You is that they make your video views look authentic. Our packages also work to bring more organic traffic since when users see popular content such as yours, it’s hard not to check in!"
      },
      {
        question:"How can I trust companies that sell YouTube views services, like Views4You offers?",
        answer:"Anytime you are thinking about trusting a company with YouTube views services, you should ask yourself a few questions: How long has this company been in business? Do they have any positive reviews? What do other people say about their services? Once you have looked into these things, you can make an informed decision about whether or not you want to trust the company. In the case of Views4You, we have been in business for years and have countless satisfied customers. We also have a five-star rating on Trustpilot, so you can be confident that we are a company you can trust. When it comes to promoting your YouTube business or product, Views4You is a clear choice."
      }
  ];